so hello everybody nice to see you here
大家好，很高兴在这里见到你
it's nice to have you here instead of
很高兴有你在这里而不是
having an ice jam events on which are on
发生冰块堵塞事件
Dean Univera
迪安大学
so today we are going to talk about CGI
所以今天我们要谈谈CGI
- and we are gonna try to make some live
-我们将尝试使一些生活
coding and CGI - so let's start by
编码和CGI-让我们开始吧
presenting myself so I'm not when
介绍自己，所以我不在
suppose you are working for reddit I'm
假设您正在为reddit工作，
the CGI to speculate and you can follow
要推测的CGI，您可以按照
me on Twitter and get up and etc I'm
我在Twitter上起床等等
also working on micro profile project so
也从事微型档案项目
will will have a big use of CGI and
将大量使用CGI，
macro macro profiles so there will be
宏宏配置文件，所以会有
some feedback from the macro profile
来自宏配置文件的一些反馈
project in CGI for the next version so
下一个版本的CGI中的项目
it's I'm very exciting about about this
我对此感到非常兴奋
so what are we going to talk about I
那我们要谈什么
will present you CGI - in two slides so
将在两张幻灯片中向您介绍CGI
if you are not totally aware of all the
如果您不完全了解所有
new stuff in CGI - I also put a link to
CGI中的新内容-我还链接了
another presentation regarding all the
关于所有
new feature of CDI - and I don't have
CDI的新功能-我没有
the time in 45 minutes to list all those
45分钟内列出所有这些时间
and make life cutting as well during
并在此期间减少生活
this presentation
这个演讲
I will check existing code I presented
我将检查现有的代码
era I think one year ago regarding
我认为一年以前
matrix integration with CDI this
与CDI的矩阵集成
integration was done in life coding but
整合是在生活编码中完成的，但
with CDI one - now I'm going to take
CDI一个-现在我要讲的是
this integration and show you how we
并向您展示我们如何
migrate it to CDI - so most of the stuff
将其迁移到CDI-大部分内容
we will see in this talk will deal with
我们将在本次演讲中看到
advanced feature on CDI and extension
CDI和扩展的高级功能
but there will be some how to set daily
但每天都会有一些设置方法
user stuff as well but if you are not
用户的东西，但如果你不是
very aware about CDI extension you have
非常了解您拥有的CDI扩展
to - to keep focus - to get it so what
为了-保持专注-得到它
are we going to do we are going to
我们要去做吗？
switch the existing test
切换现有测试
are in this project and use the new CIA
在这个项目中，并使用新的中央情报局
C feature to launch our test so the test
C功能启动我们的测试
currently are using our kuleana we will
目前正在使用我们的kuleana
use CGI SC to launch them and after that
使用CGI SC启动它们，然后
we will migrate the existing matrix
我们将迁移现有矩阵
extension to CDI 2 if we have time I
如果有时间我可以扩展到CDI 2
hope so
希望如此
if the live demo gods will be with us I
如果现场演示的神将与我们同在，我
add a NASA Kanu's event to the to the
将NASA卡努事件添加到
project as well and we will finished ok
项目也一样，我们会完成的
so let's get started so what's new in CG
让我们开始吧，CG的新功能
I took two slides so we added the
我拍了两张幻灯片，所以我们添加了
support for traversing as we are running
在运行时支持遍历
in Java C we had to add feature to to a
在Java C中，我们必须将功能添加到
low activation of request context
请求上下文激活率低
because request context doesn't have al
因为请求上下文没有
to say the same meaning in Java C that
说在Java C中相同的含义是
it could have in Java EE so we added a
它可能在Java EE中有，所以我们添加了一个
feature to activate this context in the
功能来激活该上下文
context art of Java C but it can also be
Java C的上下文艺术，但也可以是
used on Java we had a lot of
用在Java上，我们有很多
announcements on event so the most
事件公告，所以最
important announcement being the a
重要的公告是
synchronous event support and the event
同步事件支持和事件
ordering support so you can check as you
订购支持，以便您可以随时检查
see you can check the the the talk in
看到你可以查看谈话内容
the link below to have all the details
以下链接包含所有详细信息
we also added an spawned to interceptor
我们还为拦截器添加了一个生成的
so now you can use Interceptor on
所以现在您可以在
produce bin before it wasn't possible so
在不可能之前生产垃圾箱
now you can add int asymptotic protein
现在您可以添加int渐近蛋白
we also add some helpers like the
我们还添加了一些帮助程序，例如
built-in annotation literals so it's not
内置注释文字，因此不是
a big deal but now you won't have to
很大，但是现在您不必
create on your own your own annotation
自己创建自己的注释
literal to to create an annotation
用于创建注释的文字
instance and we introduced the
实例，我们介绍了
configurator API which we'll go and see
配置器API，我们将去看看
a lot in this talk so the feature that
在这次谈话中很多，所以功能
we will use in this talk is the support
我们将在本次演讲中使用的是支持
for Java C the event announcement
Java C事件公告
perhaps in the end with the synchronous
也许最终与同步
observer the built-in annotation literal
观察者内置注释文字
in the config configurator API okay so
在config configurator API中，这样
that's the two slide for CDI - if you
这是CDI的两张幻灯片-如果您
want to know more about CDI to learning
想要了解更多有关CDI的知识
kiss is below okay so let's start with
接吻是可以的，所以让我们开始吧
the existing project matrix CDI so a big
现有的项目矩阵CDI很大
a big a fast review of the matrix
快速了解矩阵
project so matrix is a very simple
项目，所以矩阵非常简单
project from drop Rosati
来自Drop Rosati的项目
it provides you a different matrix type
它为您提供了不同的矩阵类型
so we have control ganj matter time a
所以我们可以控制时间
written use it to a matrix on your hand
书面使用它到你手上的矩阵
a project so you can use different
一个项目，以便您可以使用不同的项目
reporter method to to get the
记者方法来获得
information
信息
J mix console the log etc you have in
J混合控制台日志等
the center of the of the project a
项目的中心a
metric registry well all the all your
指标注册表以及所有
metrics are stored and drop wizard
指标存储和删除向导
provide you with annotation that you can
为您提供注释，您可以
use on your own framework to implement
使用您自己的框架来实施
AOP so to be able to annotate a method
AOP这样就能注释方法
or class we have time to count etc but
或课时我们有时间算，等等，但是
there is no code behind this you have to
背后没有代码，您必须
develop it and that's it so that's for a
开发它，就是这样，这是为了
quick review of the prasada and now last
快速回顾的prasada，现在最后
year we created the integration of the
年，我们创建了
adopter of metrics with CDI so what did
采用CDI的指标，那么做了什么
we do we achieved the following goal we
我们做到了以下目标
added the capacity to produce inject
增加了生产注射剂的能力
multiple metrics so metrics are the
多个指标，因此指标是
timer cones metal etc of the same type
定时锥金属等
so we can produce them we have Cydia we
所以我们可以生产它们，我们有Cydia我们
added all the code needed to have the
添加了拥有
matrix annotation usable as interceptor
矩阵注解可用作拦截器
and we also added the fact that if you
我们还添加了一个事实，如果您
access matrix
访问矩阵
through cd-i with the @inject annotation
通过cd-i和@inject批注
or through the metric registry a
或通过度量标准注册表a
classical way of getting access to do
访问的经典方式
those metrics to get the same matrix if
这些指标可以得到相同的矩阵，如果
you use the same name which is not the
您使用的名称不是
obligatory the case because monitor our
由于监视我们
guests because you when you ask for a
客人，因为当您要求
metric to the metric registry registry
度量标准注册表注册表的度量标准
and this metric sorry doesn't exist it
而这个指标对不起不存在
is created automatically so we started
是自动创建的，所以我们开始了
from here so this is very basic code
从这里开始，这是非常基本的代码
using metric so no CDI here so here you
使用指标，所以这里没有CDI，所以在这里您
see there is I have an class helper with
看到我有一个班主任
the registry which is a static field and
注册表是一个静态字段，
I have a method for which I want to have
我有一种想要的方法
a timer so what what I do is to ask to
一个计时器，所以我要问的是
the registry and timer call my timer if
注册表和计时器调用我的计时器，如果
this eat this timer exist
这个吃这个计时器存在
I get the existing timer if it doesn't
如果没有，我会得到现有的计时器
matrix crates for me I use this timeout
矩阵板条箱对我来说我用这个超时
to start to measure time with the time
开始用时间来衡量时间
of context I do all the stuff I have to
就上下文而言，我要做的所有事情
do in a try-catch block and in the final
在try-catch程序段和最终程序中执行
block I stop the timer so that's very
阻止我停止计时器，这非常
basic code without CDI and in the end
最后没有CDI的基本代码
after the integration we ended there so
整合之后，我们就这样结束了
we added the capacity to produce
我们增加了生产能力
different metrics so here we are
不同的指标，所以我们在这里
producing two timer one called my timer
产生两个计时器，一个叫做我的计时器
and second one called my second timer
第二个叫我的第二个计时器
and the real original and the capacity
以及真正的原件和容量
to use the annotation provided with
使用随附的注释
metrics so here we use the attend
指标，因此在这里我们使用出席
annotation and we say ok this method
注解，我们说好的方法
should be
应该
time to say Monsieur biometrics with the
是时候与
time of my time also we all will have
我的时间，我们所有人都会
the my timer timer sorry
我的计时器计时器抱歉
retrieved from matrix registry and the
从矩阵注册表中检索
time of the execution of the method will
该方法的执行时间将
be recorded so that's what the current
被记录下来，这就是当前
code is doing
代码正在做
so now let's visit this code a bit
现在让我们来看一下这段代码
because if we want to migrate it to do
因为如果我们想迁移它来做
CDI to it perhaps it's better to to get
CDI可能更好
it yeah it's there so let's start with
是的，在那里，所以让我们开始吧
the the test of the project to be sure
确定项目的测试
that we are testing things in
我们正在测试的东西
interesting things so this test right
有趣的事情，所以这个测试正确
now is using arquillian everybody knows
现在正在使用Arquillian每个人都知道
that Killian okay so for those who don't
基利安好吧，对于那些不这样做的人
artyom is the way to build a micro
artyom是构建微型计算机的方式
package of your application with all the
所有的应用程序包
components you need and I have several
您需要的组件，我有几个
like environment but you have a lot of
像环境，但是你有很多
different plug-in frottage and so you
不同的插件程序，所以你
can decide what you want but IRRI it it
可以决定你想要什么，但是IRRI
needs to to other java ee lights with
需要与其他java ee灯配合使用
CDI deployment and use the feature of
CDI部署和使用功能
CDI so you can with italian you can use
CDI，因此您可以使用意大利语使用
the art injection your test to inject
您要测试的艺术注入
different beam so in Anarkali and test
所以在Anarkali和测试中使用不同的光束
you have a method annotated at
你有一个方法在
deployment the static method in this
在此部署静态方法
method you describe what you are
您描述自己的方法
creating in what you are putting in your
创造你所投入的东西
archive so here I'm creating sorry I am
存档，所以我在这里对不起
creating an archive called test at work
创建一个称为“工作中测试”的档案
and I'm putting all the elements in the
我将所有元素都放在
package or oxidizer matrix I also you
包装或氧化剂基质我也是你
and also add information from outside so
并从外面添加信息
I'm putting in my war both jar the
我都把战争放在罐子里
metrics core and the metrics annotation
指标核心和指标注释
so I can package it
所以我可以打包
in the in the world to opponent all this
在世界上与所有这些对手
information and of course I add the
信息，当然我添加了
beans xml2 activates idiot and yeah
bean xml2激活白痴，是的
and lastly nightly I'm activating the
每天晚上，我激活
extension so I have an extension we will
扩展名，所以我有一个扩展名，我们将
see it after that I am adding this
看到之后，我要添加它
extension here in the package and I
扩展在这里包和我
return
返回
yak I so I can take this and make the
牛我所以我可以拿这个做
deployment my tests are simple so the
部署我的测试很简单，所以
first test is we are testing should
第一个测试是我们正在测试应该
interceptor be code so I'm calling a
拦截器是代码，所以我打电话给
method on the MGB bin which is injected
MGB仓上注入的方法
here if we look at this method you can
在这里，如果我们看看这种方法，你可以
see that oops sorry
看到抱歉
you can see that this method is
您可以看到此方法是
annotated with at timed with the my
在与我的时间注释
timer timer timer and we want to check
计时器计时器计时器，我们要检查
that the timer was in the school during
那位计时器在学校期间
between the call so we are testing here
通话之间，所以我们在这里测试
so we are getting the timer called my
所以我们得到了一个叫做我的计时器
timer and we are getting the information
计时器，我们正在获取信息
how many times were called and we are
多少次被称为
doing an assertion here the second test
在第二次测试中进行断言
is the test about having injected
是关于注射的测试
metrics through CGI and retrieved
通过CGI度量并检索
metrics through the metric resist which
通过度量抵制来度量
is the street being the same I repeat
我重复的街道是一样的吗
again when you are doing this with the
再次当你用
street timer and you put a name here if
街头定时器，如果您在此处输入名字，
this name wasn't already used if you
如果您尚未使用此名称，
didn't already try to reach with metrics
尚未尝试达到指标
with nan my timer it will be created
与南我的计时器将被创建
automatically so the idea here is to
自动，所以这里的想法是
make sure that the timer I object
确保我反对的计时器
each year with the name my timer is the
每年我的计时器名称是
same than the knob sorry then the timer
与旋钮相同，对不起定时器
are rich with it with the same name from
富含同名的
the registry we are doing this test ok
注册表，我们正在做这个测试确定
and
和
yeah and lastly I'm interested in the
是的，最后我对
fact that all the matrix I have declared
我已经声明的所有矩阵的事实
in my program my application are
在我的程序中，我的应用程序是
registered in the registry that that's
在注册表中注册的
the last test okay so if we if we go to
最后的测试还可以，如果我们去
the to the extension that that does the
对执行该操作的扩展名
magic hero so my CDI extension who is
魔术英雄，所以我的CDI扩展名是
not familiar with CGI extension here
这里不熟悉CGI扩展
okay Oh only one guy great sorry for you
好吧，只有一个家伙，对不起你
I'm going little back and CJ assumption
我很少退缩和CJ假设
so extensions are a way to modify all
所以扩展是一种修改所有
the metadata we have in CDI so mainly to
我们在CDI中拥有的元数据主要是
register new bean to modify existing
注册新的Bean修改现有的
bean and to modify add annotation
bean并修改添加注释
roughly add annotation an existing
粗略地添加现有注释
element to add feature to the to
要向中添加功能的元素
determine so here in this extension we
确定在此扩展中，我们
have a different kind of method so for
有另一种方法
instance the first method is very simple
实例第一种方法很简单
we are observing the before being
我们正在观察之前
discovery lifecycle even so when you're
发现生命周期，即使您处于
when your container CGI called my
当您的集装箱CGI叫我的
starting it fires all kind of seventh in
启动它在第七种
certain order so here we are listening
一定的顺序，所以我们在这里听
to the first event before bin discovery
到bin发现之前的第一个事件
and in the beef up in discovery I can
在发现中我可以
add one annotation as the qualifier as a
添加一个注释作为限定符
CDI qualifier so here I'm taking the
CDI资格赛，所以我在这里
metric annotation that I don't all that
指标注释，我不是全部
come from the metric and I'm adding it
来自指标，我将其添加
as a qualifier the second
作为预选赛第二
method here is about interceptor so I
这里的方法是关于拦截器的，所以我
want to check the at timed annotation
要检查定时注释
coming from matrix and say ok now it
来自矩阵，现在说好吧
should be an interceptor binding because
应该是拦截器绑定，因为
when I get it it's nothing it's only an
当我明白了它什么都没有的时候
annotation so I want to declare it as an
批注，所以我想将其声明为
interceptor binding so I'm doing the
拦截器绑定，所以我正在
same I'm observing the same event you
我正在观察同一事件
see here and I'm using the before in
看到这里，我在之前使用
discovery method which is called ad
发现方法，称为广告
interceptor binding in this method I
拦截器绑定在这种方法我
have to add a new data type of the
必须添加新的数据类型
Interceptor binding I want to add I
拦截器绑定我要添加我
could I could have add the class
我可以增加课程吗
directly but it's not possible here
直接但是在这里不可能
because the if we go to the time
因为如果我们去时间
annotation you see here the time
您在这里看到的注释时间
annotation as to member name and
关于成员姓名和
absolute the problem is if you if we
绝对的问题是，如果您
don't add information to this member
不要向该成员添加信息
they will be used to distinguish two
他们将被用来区分两个
different version of the annotation so
注释的版本不同
if you write for instance at kind of my
如果你写一些我的话
timer of our at time of my time or two
我们一两个时间的定时器
there will be two different interceptor
会有两个不同的拦截器
bindings so I have to create two
绑定，所以我必须创建两个
different interceptor one for the at
在的不同拦截器
time my
时间我的
my timer and at time my timer - so I
我的计时器，还有我的计时器-所以我
have to add specific meta annotations on
必须在上添加特定的元注释
those number
那些号码
it's the non-binding annotation that's
这是非约束性注释
the reason why I cannot add directly I
我不能直接添加的原因
cannot add directly the time class here
无法在此处直接添加时间类别
I have to create an annotated child
我必须创建一个带注释的孩子
which will add those non binding on all
这将对所有未绑定
the members so I have created an
成员，所以我创建了一个
implementation and that's what we are
实施，这就是我们
doing in CDI extension most of the time
大多数时候都在进行CDI扩展
implementing the spi to add our feet
实施spi以增加我们的脚
earlier so we will have a look at that
较早，所以我们将看看
later but I created my own and I tried
后来，但我创建了自己的，我尝试了
to add those non-binding as definite the
将那些非约束性的添加为确定的
third is a very interesting part of the
第三是很有趣的部分
extension it's the part of the extension
扩展是扩展的一部分
that catch all the produced metrics so
捕获所有产生的指标，因此
here I observed all the producer that
在这里，我观察了所有制片人
define metric so I'm doing this because
定义指标，所以我这样做是因为
I'm observing the even process producer
我正在观察均匀的生产者
the wild card here say this this
这里的通配符说这个
producer can be in any class but they
生产者可以在任何阶层，但他们
should produce see see being anything
应该产生看到什么
that extends metric so all the producer
扩展了指标，所以所有生产者
that produce metric will be will trigger
生产指标将被触发
this this lifecycle events
这个生命周期事件
I'm also injecting the be manager I can
我也在注入我可以做的经理
do that in any observer the lifecycle
在任何观察者的生命周期中做到这一点
event what i'm doing here is i'm testing
我在这里做的事情是我正在测试
do I have the metric annotation on this
我对此有指标注释吗
on this metric producer if it's the case
如果是这种情况，则在此指标生成器上
I retrieved the name and with this name
我检索了这个名字并使用了这个名字
I create my own producer that will do
我创建了自己的制作人
some magic stuff we will see that later
一些魔术的东西，我们稍后会看到
but it roughly it will check if it will
但它会大致检查是否
check if the matrix is already in
检查矩阵是否已经在
registry if it's the case it instead of
如果是这样，而不是注册表
creating the metric it gives me give me
创建指标，它给了我
the metric in the registry and if it
注册表中的指标以及是否
doesn't exist in the registry it welted
所关联的注册表中不存在
address to the registry amount and
地址到注册表金额，以及
returns it okay sorry
归还吧，对不起
and the last method in the in this
还有这个中的最后一个方法
extension in fact is the method that
扩展实际上就是
makes sure that all the metrics that are
确保所有的指标
declared as a producer will be created
声明为生产者将被创建
before the application runs that that
在应用程序运行之前
unsure the fact that I will have the
不确定我将拥有
same metric in a registry and metric
注册表和指标中的相同指标
that in that I will inject okay so we
在那我会注入好，所以我们
can run this test right now I will go
现在可以运行此测试，我将去
even deeper in the code after that and
之后甚至更深层的代码
we know if I can run it right now yeah
我们知道我现在是否可以运行它
so I'm launching the test so my eye I
所以我开始测试，我的眼睛我
didn't mention it but I just use testing
没有提到它，但我只是使用测试
G but you can use g-unit without in
G，但您可以不使用in
program I'm using test testing G because
我使用测试程序G的程序，因为
it will be easier later with the CDI C
以后使用CDI C会更容易
to bootstrap the container so I have my
引导容器，以便我有我的
three tests passing and I want to show
三个测试通过了，我想证明
you that this code here is not dummy
你这个代码不是假的
code or funny stuff so if I command one
代码或有趣的东西，所以如果我命令一个
of those method I think some of the my
这些方法的方法，我认为
tests one pass yeah so here I commented
测试一个通过是的，所以我在这里评论
you see a comment at the the part that
您会在该部分看到评论
at the time the as interceptor binding
当时的as拦截器绑定
and
和
the test that is called should the time
所谓的测试应该是时间
intercept or cold
拦截或冷
don't pass so it's not it's a real code
不通过，不是真正的代码
here okay whoa okay so let's start
好的，哇，好的，让我们开始吧
perhaps I have some slide on the topic
也许我在这个话题上有一些幻灯片
okay let's start with the switch to se
好吧，让我们从切换到se开始
so before switching to AC we're going to
所以在切换到交流之前，我们要
switch to CDI to so to switch to CDI - I
切换到CDI，以便切换到CDI-我
have to go in my plan XML and I have to
必须输入我的计划XML，而我必须
change do you see is it readable okay so
改变，你看到它可读吗
I'm gonna change the version of CDI
我要更改CDI的版本
which is here and I have also to change
在这里，我也必须改变
the version of the implementation so
实施的版本
right now I'm using wild two four five
现在我正在使用野生的二四五
I'm going to switch to the last version
我将切换到最新版本
of well three which is the reference
三口井中，这是参考
implementation for see yeah I will the
实现，是的，我会
wild free that oh that one final and I
野性的自由，哦那个决赛，我
have a change I guess
我猜有变化
let me check no it should should be okay
让我检查不应该应该没事
so now let me show you that we are
现在让我告诉你我们
running CDI - so if we if we look at the
运行CDI-因此，如果我们看一下
big engine if we look at the console
大引擎，如果我们看一下控制台
here you see that the version of well is
在这里，您会看到井的版本是
two four five okay if I run my test
二四五好吧，如果我运行测试
again should be free oh one crossing
再次应该是自由的哦
finger okay okay you see free one so I
手指好吧好吧，你看到一个免费的，所以我
I've switched to CI - oh right now let's
我已切换为CI-哦，现在让我们
do a bit more so we are going to use the
多做一点，所以我们将使用
CDI SC bootstrap API so it's looking
CDI SC引导程序API，因此看起来
like this so we introduced
像这样，我们介绍了
two new interface one interface and one
两个新界面一个界面和一个
class by the way so the SC container
顺便说一句，所以SC容器
container interface and the SE cotner
容器接口和SE cotner
initializer interface
初始化接口
so we've initialized oh you have a
所以我们已经初始化了哦，你有一个
pattern you can create a new instance of
模式，您可以创建一个新实例
the initializer you have a lot of
初始化程序你有很多
feature we can disable beam discovery
我们可以禁用波束发现的功能
and add all you been one by one you can
并一一加进来
add the property here we are in class
在我们上课的地方添加属性
and in the end when everything is ok for
最后一切都好
you when wa you have the right
你什么时候你有权利
configuration for your Europe Nara you
您的欧洲Nara您的配置
call the initialize and it returns you
调用初始化，它返回您
living now with the of the of s equals
现在与s的of等于
no type so here in the example I'm using
没有类型，所以在我使用的示例中
the container to retrieve a bin of type
容器以检索类型为bin的容器
myself okay very simple because the
我自己很简单，因为
container is implementing the instance
容器正在实现实例
interface if you are using the
界面（如果您使用的是
programmatic look up in Cydia you
在Cydia中进行程序化查找
probably know a lemon okay so we are
大概知道一个柠檬好吧，所以我们
going to use this in our test so if I go
要在我们的测试中使用它，如果我去
back to the test which is here I'm going
回到我要去的测试中
to remove all the arquillians stuff so
删除所有arquillians的东西，所以
here I will not externally on and I will
在这里，我不会在外部，我会
remove this method okay
删除此方法好吗
so let's create a method to launch after
因此，让我们创建一种在之后启动的方法
something like
就像是
okay start me up I don't have the music
好吧，让我开始，我没有音乐
I won't sing okay so I will use what we
我不会唱歌，所以我会用我们
just saw so I'm creating a sip of
刚刚看到，所以我正在创建一口
nursery and a sea container viable with
苗圃和一个可行的海运集装箱
the right spelling and using the a sea
正确的拼写和使用大海
container initializer creating a new
容器初始化程序创建一个新的
instance and adding the the package for
实例并添加包
my test so I have to add so I can add
我的测试，所以我必须添加，以便我可以添加
the package through the class so I can
通过班级的包裹，所以我可以
say okay add the package with the the
说好的，请添加带有
class so I can take this class so I'm
上课，所以我可以上这堂课
adding all the stuff in the test and I
在测试中添加所有内容，我
can also add I have also to add all the
也可以添加我还必须添加所有
the package and in the project so I'm
包和项目中，所以我
going to type metrics extension class so
要输入指标扩展类，以便
I'm adding here all the packages in the
我在这里添加所有软件包
test and in the project from forth of
测试和在项目中
this class I also have to add the
这个课我也要加
extension so cutting the add extension
扩展名，因此剪切添加扩展名
and putting ear the the class of my
并听取我的班级
extension matrix extension
扩展矩阵扩展
[Music]
[音乐]
whoa
哇
I have a new spelling metric extension
我有一个新的拼写指标扩展名
okay and should be okay so I can call
好的，应该还可以，我可以打电话给
the initialize here with the dots will
用点初始化在这里
be better okay and so now I have my
会更好，所以现在我有了我的
container so if my test here weren't
容器，所以如果我的测试不在
using injection I could stop there I
使用注射我可以停在那里
love the company it's ok but you see
喜欢公司，还可以，但是你知道
here I'm injecting stuff in my test so I
我在测试中注入一些东西，所以我
have to do an extra trick to perform
必须做一个额外的技巧来执行
injection on my test so that I have to
注射我的测试，所以我必须
retrieve the bin manager so what I'm
检索垃圾箱管理器，所以我
doing here could be done in g-unit
在这里可以以g为单位
extension or a testing G listener to
扩展或测试G侦听器
have something cleaner so it's only to
有更清洁的东西，所以只
show you so I can retrieve the be
给你看，这样我可以找回
manager from the container
集装箱经理
ok with the bin manager I will be able
好的垃圾桶管理器，我将能够
to create what is called an injection an
创建所谓的注射
injunction target so let's go for the
禁制令的目标，所以让我们去
injection target and the type will be
注射目标和类型
the my the type of the test class and
我的测试班级类型和
this injection target will be created by
这个注射目标将由
the bin manager I have to provide sorry
我必须提供的垃圾桶经理
for that I have to provide an annotated
为此，我必须提供一个注释
type so created era ok should be ok
这样创建的时代应该还可以
I'm gonna be more readable if I do
如果这样做，我会更具可读性
something like this okay and after that
这样的事情还可以，之后
I will use this injection target to
我将使用这个注射目标
perform injection on my test object so
对我的测试对象执行注射
I'm injecting this and I'm creating a
我正在注入这个，我正在创建一个
creational context as it's not been with
创造上下文，因为它不存在
the with the scope I creating a
与我创建的范围
creational context if null so I have a
创建性上下文，如果为null，那么我有一个
default default wanna and last but not
默认默认要和最后但不是
least if I want this code to be started
至少如果我想启动此代码
before all my tests I will use them at
在我进行所有测试之前，我将在
before class so in test ng you can use
上课之前，您可以在测试中使用
the this before class on non-static
非静态上课前
method which is not the case in g-unit
g单位不是这种方法
reason why I switch to test engine like
我之所以选择测试引擎的原因
this but there is a some trick even jig
这，但有一个技巧，甚至夹具
need five I guess I saw that so here
需要五个，我想我看到了，所以在这里
what I'm what I've done I removed all
我所做的事情我删除了所有
the occasional reference and created my
偶尔参考并创建了我的
own boot section so it's okay to be
自己的引导区，所以可以
honest it's a bit messy the part here
老实说，这里的部分有点混乱
but you can imagine having your own is
但是你可以想象拥有自己的是
now doing that automatically so now I
现在自动执行此操作
can launch my test based only and CISC
可以只根据我的考试和CISC进行测试
and it's not working
而且不起作用
okay so yeah well yeah that's normal
好吧，是的，这是正常的
why do I have this because I only add to
为什么会有这个，因为我只添加到
my project name limitation for Travis I
我对Travis I的项目名称限制
don't have all the class for Travis so
没有特拉维斯的所有课程，所以
you have to change in my poem all the
你必须改变我的诗
the dependency for well taking a bigger
对更大的依赖
package forward so let's get sued okay
打包前进，让我们起诉吧
that's so I don't need
那就是我不需要
I don't exactly on anymore so yeah I can
我不会再这样了，是的，我可以
add dependency not sure I will find it
添加依赖关系不确定我会找到它
so well yeah it's this one well as she
很好，是的，这就是她
shaded and I'm going to take the last
阴影，我要走最后一个
one which is which is not here yeah so
一个不在这里的是的，所以
free one final so I'm adding this I'm
免费获得一个决赛，所以我要添加这个
removing the the dependency of well only
消除对井的依赖
for Java and putting the one for Java C
Java，将其用于Java C
otherwise I won't be able to bootstrap
否则我将无法引导
documentation it was to make sure that
文档是为了确保
everyone was following okay so now I'm
每个人都在跟踪，所以现在我
running the test with my own container
用我自己的容器运行测试
so yeah you see that I have new
所以是的，你看到我有新的
information here regarding the
有关此处的信息
transactional service that I don't have
我没有的交易服务
but I don't need transaction in my test
但我不需要考试
oh okay so the interest of that is a
哦，好吧，那是一个
Korean maybe bit avis in some music some
韩国人在某些音乐中可能有点偏爱
use case so there you can use the
用例，因此您可以使用
minimum CDI stuff to play your test and
参加测试的最低CDI资料和
to show you that to show you that the
向您展示，向您展示
this bootstrapping is working everywhere
这个引导程序无处不在
I will switch my implementation and use
我将切换我的实现和使用
the over implementation which is open
开放的过度实施
web beans and I have an open web beans
Web bean，我有一个开放的Web bean
se which is so the last version of open
se这是打开的最后一个版本
web beans se is the 201 so era
Web bean se是201 so时代
I removed well switch to open web beans
我删除了很好的开关以打开Web Bean
running the test the same way so I don't
以相同的方式运行测试，所以我不
change my code or need the dependency
更改我的代码或需要依赖
Cresson finger
手指手指
so it's working by the way you see that
所以它以您看到的方式起作用
open web in ZZZ more verbose at the
在ZZZ中打开网页的详细信息
lunchtime but can be interesting because
午餐时间，但可能很有趣，因为
it lists all the all the bins discovered
它列出了所有发现的垃圾箱
at boot time ok so now we we are using
在启动时好，所以现在我们正在使用
CD is so let's let's go to our extension
CD是这样，让我们​​开始扩展
and start me right check no time wow I'm
马上开始给我检查，哇
speaking to ok
说话还可以
let's start with the first part here we
让我们从第一部分开始
don't have to do anything
不用做任何事
metric as qualifier we can keep it
指标作为限定词，我们可以保留它
because we are only using a class it
因为我们只使用一个类
becomes interesting here you see we are
变得有趣，在这里你看到我们
adding an interceptor binding we've
添加拦截器绑定
annotated type I have to create it so
带注释的类型，我必须创建它
what is doing this class an attitude
这堂课的态度是什么
type with all method non binding
所有方法均非绑定类型
so in this annotated type I'm only
所以在这个带注释的类型中，我只是
decorating an annotated type so here
装饰带注释的类型，所以这里
delegate and I'm returning all the
代表，我要归还所有
value of a delegate made the litigated
代表的价值提出诉讼
under data type except when I asked for
在数据类型下，除非我要求
the methods when I asked from the
当我从
methods I will take those methods and
方法我将采用这些方法，
Easter instead of threatening the
复活节而不是威胁
methods I will replace them by a
方法我将用
non-binding and attitude method which
非约束和态度方法
decorates the method bit complicated
装饰方法有点复杂
the idea is to say ok I want to to be
这个想法是说好吧，我想成为
able to say I have non binding on this
可以说我对此没有约束力
method where it's not on the original
不在原始位置上的方法
source
资源
so this non-binding annotation method is
所以这个非绑定注释方法是
doing quite the same and it's only doing
做的完全一样，只是在做
stuff regarding the addition of non
关于添加非的东西
binding to the method so when I ask for
绑定到方法，所以当我要求
the annotation on the method I take the
我采用的方法上的注释
original annotations and add non binding
原始注释并添加非绑定
and when I am asked about the presence
当我被问到存在
of non binding if it's if it's that I
非约束力的如果是我
returned true so I have for this little
返回true，所以我有这点
feature of ideal non binding on all my
理想的约束力对我所有
element I have two class here plus an
元素我在这里有两个课，再加上一个
upper class here non binding literal to
上层阶级在这里没有约束文字
have some thinking so free class free
有一些想法，所以免费上课免费
classes I will replace replace it with
我将替换的类将其替换为
simple CDI to code so yeah I can use the
简单的CDI编码，是的，我可以使用
new feature from Cydia the configure
Cydia的新功能配置
interceptor binding so instead of adding
拦截器绑定，因此无需添加
my interceptor binding like that I can
这样我的拦截器绑定
configure it I can get the methods of
配置它，我可以得到的方法
the Interceptor beneath will close that
下方的拦截​​器将关闭
and for reached of this method I will
对于这种方法，我会
take the method and I don't need the
采取的方法，我不需要
curly bracket but anyway and I will add
大括号，但无论如何，我会添加
non-binding I'm not using the I'm not
不具有约束力的我不使用不
using the non-binding literal I created
使用我创建的非绑定文字
anymore because I have now literal in
不再，因为我现在有文字
the spec and that's it
规格就是这样
oops I mean what's the problem here
糟糕，我的意思是这是什么问题
yeah I have to I have to go sorry I have
是的，我必须要我对不起
to give them of course I have to give
给他们当然我必须给
the the class okay so yeah
这个班好吧，是的
I removed three big class and two big
我删除了三个大班和两个大班
class and one once more and put
上课再讲一次
something very small instead let's try
很小的东西让我们尝试
if it's working
如果在工作
yeah you have ten minutes to show you
是的，你有十分钟给你看
the D and H it will be quite easy next
D和H接下来会很容易
is one of the most tricky part of the
是最棘手的部分之一
code so the ID here I'm going to show
代码，以便在此显示ID
you the idea error is when I detect this
你的想法错误是当我检测到这个
in my code so I'm producing here a timer
在我的代码中，所以我在这里产生一个计时器
which is a metric it extends them the
这是一个指标，它扩展了他们
metric it implements the metrics
指标，它实现指标
interface I want to be able to not
我想不能的界面
execute this code each time I want to be
每当我想成为时执行此代码
able to check the registry if I'm timer
可以检查注册表，如果我是计时器
if a metric if the name my time are
如果是一个指标，如果我的名字是
exist if it exists I returned the
存在（如果存在）我返回了
existing one if it doesn't I create the
现有的如果不是我创建
metric add to the registry and return
指标添加到注册表并返回
the stuff okay so in fact this this code
东西还可以，所以实际上这段代码
is the way that my user will be declare
是我的用户将被声明的方式
my the metrics and I'm adding the next
我的指标，我要添加下一个
and the next function the tricky part
接下来的功能是棘手的部分
that will avoid creating extra metrics
这样可以避免创建额外的指标
if it's not needed so to do that here in
如果不需要的话在这里做
my 1/2 code I have to descend to listen
我的1/2代码我必须下降才能听
the process producer as I show a
我展示的过程生产者
beginning I'm retrieving the metric
开始我要获取指标
annotation on the producer because I
在生产者上标注，因为我
need the name to achieve the name of the
需要名称来获得名称
of Dmytryk I'm requesting okay and I'm
Dmytryk我要求还可以，我是
changing the producer that was
改变原来的生产者
intercepted by the observer by a project
观察者被一个项目拦截
I created myself so that's the new
我创造了自己，这就是新的
metric producer it's the same that we
公制生产者，与我们相同
see before era metric producer decorate
在度量标准生产者装饰之前看
the existing producer okay and call
现有的生产者还可以，请致电
unlimited of the decorated producer
无限的装饰生产者
except when it comes to produce the
除非涉及到生产
element so when I want to produce the
元素，所以当我想产生
element I'm retrieving the registry here
元素我在这里检索注册表
it's a bit complicated we will see that
有点复杂，我们会看到
we to be simplified after that I'm
我们要简化之后
testing does the registry contain a
测试注册表是否包含
metric with the name I received if it's
指标与我收到的名称（如果是
the case if it's not the case I'll
如果不是这种情况，我会
register this new matrix by calling the
通过调用
produce method of the decorated producer
装饰生产者的生产方法
and in the end I return the matrix from
最后，我从
the registry so I will use this code but
注册表，所以我将使用此代码，但
I will use it in simple simpler way so I
我将以更简单的方式使用它，所以我
will get rid of this class go back to my
将摆脱这个班回到我
extension yes
扩展是
okay so era this line will be used
好吧，这个时代将被使用
anymore and I will use so PP is my
不再使用了，所以我会用PP
process producer and I have a configure
流程生产者，我有一个配置
producer in it the configure producer
生产者在其中配置生产者
allow me to define a function to produce
让我定义一个要产生的函数
the element the beam so I will produce
光束的元素，所以我会产生
its Weaver
它的韦弗
so I receive a creational context the CD
所以我收到了一个创作背景CD
I will provide it for me and and I will
我会为我提供它，而我会
put the code sorry I will put the code
把代码对不起，我会把代码
here that I copied from my previous
这是我以前复制的
producer and I will check a few things
制片人，我将检查几件事
so here I don't need that anymore
所以在这里我不再需要了
because I have a very convenient way to
因为我有一个非常方便的方法
reach with instance in CDI - and this
在CDI中达到实例-这
convenient way
方便的方法
use the bin manager so I can create an
使用垃圾桶管理器，这样我就可以创建一个
instance so that's the instance you know
实例，这就是您所知道的实例
as the programmatic lookup mechanism so
作为程序化查找机制
I can do this here this instance I can
我可以在此实例中做到这一点
select metric registry type okay and I
选择度量标准注册表类型，然后我
can get instance so here I have a simple
可以获取实例，所以在这里我有一个简单的
way to reach with the registry here I'm
我在这里到达注册表的方式
not using metric name but name which is
不使用指标名称，而是使用
here okay the same here
这里好，这里一样
okay and the same here it's no more see
好吧，这里不再一样了
but it's expert II I'm not even sure
但这不是专家II
that I need that and I need to reach
我需要那个，我需要达到
with this decorate so let's do this
用这个装饰，让我们做这个
error so it's a producer of G
错误，所以它是G的生产者
okay decorate and it's I retrieve it
好，装饰，是我找回来的
from the process producer okay so I
从流程生产者那里好，所以我
won't need this line anymore and I don't
不再需要这条线，我也不需要
think the class I created anymore so in
认为我再创建了一个类
a very Java 8 way I can have a cleaner
我可以用Java 8做清洁工的方法
code launching the test crossing finger
代码启动测试交叉手指
okay I didn't test with open web beans
好吧，我没有用开放式Web Bean进行测试
before so it's it's alive yeah and we
在此之前，它还活着，是的，我们
have few minutes left to do the last
还剩几分钟来做最后
observer in our extension so era I have
观察者在我们这样的延伸时代
an observer that observed the event
观察事件的观察者
after the problem validation so where
问题验证后，在哪里
everything is ready to to run my
一切都准备好运行我的
application I have this event after the
应用程序后，我有此事件
plant validation and I what I want is to
工厂验证，我想要的是
trigger the creation of of all the
触发所有
producer in my application to make sure
生产者在我的应用程序中，以确保
that they are registered in the metric
他们已在指标中注册
registry to avoid the fact that I can
注册表以避免我可以
reach with different metric if I use the
如果我使用
metric 303 or if I inject the the metric
指标303，或者如果我注入指标
so era I'm going to remove this and use
所以时代我要删除它并使用
something smaller so I gonna do what
一些较小的东西，所以我要做什么
I've done before create instance so from
我已经在创建实例之前完成了
distance I can select the element I want
距离我可以选择想要的元素
to retrieve so here it will be
检索，所以在这里
metric okay but not this one it's the
指标还可以，但不是这个
yeah this one take care because they are
是的，这个人要小心，因为他们是
the metric annotation on the metric an
度量标准上的度量标准注释和
interface okay
界面还可以
and I want to retrieve all the metrics
我想检索所有指标
because I have the annotation on them so
因为我上面有注释
I will check the any Poli fire used
我将检查使用的任何Poli火
deterrent and instance okay
威慑和实例还可以
so yeah I have a correction I have a way
所以是的，我有更正，我有办法
to iterate on the collection of all the
遍历所有
metrics defined through producer in my
通过我的生产者定义的指标
application so now I can use the forage
应用程序，现在我可以使用草料了
from my collection and for each matrix
从我的收藏和每个矩阵
in fact I do nothing I want only to
实际上我什么也不想做
trigger the creation so it will trigger
触发创建，因此它将触发
the code in the producer era and make
生产者时代的代码，使
sure that all the metrics will be
确保所有指标将
registered like this and it's Mac it
像这样注册，并且是Mac
makes the code far far easier to read
使代码更容易阅读
easier to read sorry and should be ok we
较容易阅读，对不起，应该没问题，我们
finish it on that and it's nice working
完成它，这很好
ok that's it I think I don't have any
好的，就是这样，我认为我没有任何东西
time left so if you have any questions
还剩时间，如果您有任何疑问
I'd be outside ready to answer and I
我会在外面准备回答，我
encourage you to to check the slides
鼓励您检查幻灯片
regarding a CDI to a noose new feature
关于CDI的套索新功能
to have all the tournament that we are
拥有我们所有的比赛
presented in this talk thank you
在本次演讲中提出谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]